[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a statutory real estate organization?<br />&nbsp;(1) The BC Financial Services Authority<br />&nbsp;(2) The Real Estate Institute of British Columbia",
    "answer": "Which of the following is an example of a statutory real estate organization?<br />&nbsp;<strong>(1) The BC Financial Services Authority</strong><br />&nbsp;(2) The Real Estate Institute of British Columbia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The greatest bundle of rights and responsibilities that an individual can hold in land in British Columbia is a _______ _______ interest. ",
    "answer": "The greatest bundle of rights and responsibilities that an individual can hold in land in British Columbia is a <strong>fee simple</strong> interest."
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ is responsible for the local nature of real property markets.",
    "answer": "<strong>Immobility</strong> is responsible for the local nature of real property markets."
  },
  {
    "question": "The ownership of a single parcel of real estate may be divided both physically and legally.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;(2) False",
    "answer": "The ownership of a single parcel of real estate may be divided both physically and legally.<br />&nbsp;<strong>(1) True</strong><br />&nbsp;(2) False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ______ ______ ______ ______ is responsible for the licensing of real estate service providers and the general protection of the public.",
    "answer": "The <strong>BC Financial Services Authority</strong> is responsible for the licensing of real estate service providers and the general protection of the public."
  },
  {
    "question": "The immobility of real property means that land is subject to external effects known as _________.",
    "answer": "The immobility of real property means that land is subject to external effects known as <strong>externalities</strong>."
  },
  {
    "question": "When considering the durability of structures, it is important to distinguish between the _______ life and the _______ life of the structure.",
    "answer": "When considering the durability of structures, it is important to distinguish between the <strong>physical</strong> life and the <strong>economic</strong> life of the structure."
  },
  {
    "question": "The British Columbia Real Estate Association (BCREA) is an example of a ________ organization.",
    "answer": "The British Columbia Real Estate Association (BCREA) is an example of a <strong>voluntary</strong> organization."
  },
  {
    "question": "The major concern of the Real Estate Services Act is the protection of the public.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;(2) False",
    "answer": "The major concern of the Real Estate Services Act is the protection of the public.<br />&nbsp;<strong>(1) True</strong><br />&nbsp;(2) False"
  },
  {
    "question": "BCREA only attempts to address concerns that affect members in a particular geographic location within the province.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;(2) False",
    "answer": "BCREA only attempts to address concerns that affect members in a particular geographic location within the province.<br />&nbsp;(1) True<br />&nbsp;<strong>(2) False</strong>"
  }
]